Guide to the Church League of America Collection of the Research Files of Counterattack, the Wackenhut Corporation, and Karl Baarslag TAM.148
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Counterattack Research Files, 1928-1967
  - Subseries V: Individuals, 1931-1960
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Taylor, Glen; Wallace, Henry A.; Roosevelt, Eleanor; Gustavson, Dr. R. G.; Doyle, Charles A.] (14-0-220 to 14-0-230), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Indexes and "Who's Who" For Appleget, Thomas Baird to Gregg, Dr. Alan] (14-0-231 to 14-0-252), undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Indexes and "Who's Who" for Hamershlag, Howard to Wortis, Rose] (14-0-253 to 14-0-274), 1947 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Flynn, Edward J.; Bishop, Dr. Eugene L.; Ayash, Edward] (14-0-275 to 14-0-282), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Zarichney, James; Franklin, Dr. Mitchell; Livingston, Frederick; Klein, Martin; Kingsley, J. Donald] (14-0-283 to 14-0-292), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Sarvis, Guy W.; Priestly, S.E. Gerard; Mosely, Dr. Philip E.; Gleason, Leverett S.] (14-0-293 to 14-0-297), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Mendell, Dr. Martha; Ross, Lillian; Wiener, Paul Lester; Morgan, Henry; Miko, Stephen] (14-0-298 to 14-0-307), 1947-1948 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Shull, Leo; Stern, Meyer Esterkin; Vidaver, Sidney J.; Brown, Vanessa] (14-0-308 to 14-0-318), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Herman, Ruth; Kraber, Tony and Wilhelmina; Turnaski, Yankel Benjamin; Chandler, Marion H.] (14-0-319 to 14-0-330), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Smith, Randolph B.; Stokes, Thomas Lunsford Jr.; Randolph, A. Philip; Howlett, Rev. Duncan] (14-0-331 to 14-0-340), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Hobson, Laura Z.; Shaw, Bruno; Kramberg, Sam; Norris, Charles G.; Kieffer, Adah; Bakerman, Bernie] (14-0-341 to 14-0-351), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Maguire, Edward C.; Lanke, Alfred C.; Waxman, A.F.; Sockman, Rev. Ralph W.; Minkin, Sophie] (14-0-352 to 14-0-367), 1945-1948 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Reynolds, Quentin; Fritchman, Rev. Stephen H.; Shapiro, Samuel P.; Rabinowitz, Victor; Searle, Robert W.] (14-0-368 to 14-0-372), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Goldberg, Rabbi Joshua L.; Stern, Dr. Bernhad J.; Bunche, Dr. Ralph J.; Barry, Walter (a.k.a. Eisenstat, Israel)] (14-0-373 to 14-0-382), 1944, 1948 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Melby, Ernest O.; Recht, Charles; Polier, Shad; Weltfish, Dr. Gene; Gannett, Lewis] (14-0-383 to 14-0-389), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Linford, Prof. Alton A.; Houseman, John; Hall, Martin; Maietta, Julia; Golderg, B.Z.] (14-0-390 to 14-0-403), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Weber, Ferdinand Palmer; Voss, Dr. Carl Hermann; Brown, Elmer; Raskin, Jack; Warne, Prof. Colston E.] (14-0-404 to 14-0-408), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Hart, Marian; Taylor, Frank E.; Zorach, Tessim; Mangold, Helen; Wells, Charles A.; Kramer, Charles] (14-0-409 to 14-0-415), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Hurwitz, Leo; Mackenzie, Cameron; Johnson, Dr. Hewlett; Davis, Michael M. Jr.; Gluck, Esta; Carlson, Prof. Anton J.; Montgomery, Donald Ewan] (14-0-416 to 14-0-422), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Neuberger, Samuel A.; Shapiro, Samuel P.; Rabinowitz, Victor; Harris, Dr. Helen; Hammer, Armand; Rhode, Ruth Bryan Owen] (14-0-423 to 14-0-428), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Chisolm, Robert Don; McWilliams, Carey; Findly, John K.; Yankwich, Judge Leon R.; Fiering, Henry; Davis, Dr. Herbert John] (14-0-429 to 14-0-434), 1948 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Gutwillig, Mildred; Parodneck, Meyer; Turner, Jeanette; Schutzer, Arthur; Young, Thomas; Jones, Rev. John Paul; Hunt, Marsha; Scott, Allan] (14-0-435 to 14-0-442), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Tobias, Channing Heggie; Detzer, Dorothy; Sprechman, Joseph; Nelson, Steve; Houseman, John; Farrell, James Thomas; Kazin, Alfred] (14-0-443 to 14-0-451), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Olsen, Rose; Hutchins, Grace; Nash, Dr. Vernon; Voss, Dr. Carl Hermann; Anderson, Dr. Dewey; Lancaster, Burt] (14-0-452 to 14-0-457), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Brickman, Delmore; Ernst, Hugo; Tobias, Channing Heggie; Dublin, Mary; Struik, Dirk J.; Van Arsdale, Harry; Counts, Prof. George S.] (14-0-458 to 14-0-464), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Blaisdell, Thomas C. and Catherine; Sipser, Isidore Philip; Wright, Archie; Crosby, Alexander L.; Seeger, Peter] (14-0-465 to 14-0-472), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Gellis, Mortimer; Chase, Nicholas; Stanley, John J.; Levy, Joseph H.; Patterson, Frederick Douglas; Barlow, Samuel Latham Mitchill] (14-0-473 to 14-0-478), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Brameld, Theodore; McMichael, Rev. Jack R.; Klare, Charles; Shore, Jerome; Lewis, Richard; Siegel, Frank; Engelberg, Frank] (14-0-479 to 14-0-485), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Perl, Arnold; Cobb, Lee J.; Haessler, Carl; Kutcher, James; Irving, Charles; Gellhorn, Walter; Galin, Jack; Krzycki, Leo] (14-0-486 to 14-0-495), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [O'Connor, Tom; Rothbard, Samuel L.; Kuniyoshi, Yasuo; Lieber, Maxim; Schary, Dore; Bernstein, Walter; Lyon, Peter] (14-0-496 to 14-0-507), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Brodsky, Max; Meyers, Ben; Lorch, Lee; Hirschberg, Herbert; Campbell, Robert; Conway, Kurt; Field, Nowell; Watkins, John T.] (14-0-508 to 14-0-516), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Higgins, Harry B.; Reed, Philip D.; Perl, Arnold; Wolfson, Martin; Burnett, Newman H. (Nicki); Grauer, Ben; Lyon, Peter] (14-0-517 to 14-0-526), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lewis, Edna S.; Jessup, Philip C.; Philbrick, Herbert Arthur; Dale, Thelma; Brown, Bruce K.; Cutler, Bertram] (14-0-527 to 14-0-532), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Matles, James; Plunkert, William J.; Robertson, Milton; Hausman, Howard L.; Shapiro, Harold L.] (14-0-533 to 14-0-537), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Kline, Herbert; Lev, Ray; Boyer, Charles; Kelton, Pert; DaSilva, Howard; White, Theodore H.; Robertson, Milton; Weisner, Louis; Torre, Louis] (14-0-538 to 14-0-547), 1946, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Dimock, Marshall Edward; Carter, Mr. and Mrs. Edward C.; Witt, Herbert; Van Orden, Katherine Armitage; Pollack, Arthur; Aries, Robert S.] (14-0-548 to 14-0-554), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Gruenberg, Sidonie Matsner; Williams, Dave; Armitage, Merle; Klein, Adelaide; Hammett, Dashiell; Williams, Mary Lou; Wilson, Teddy (Jazz musician)] (14-0-555 to 14-0-562), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Commager, Henry Steele; Ward, Lynd Kendall; Green (Greenberg), Charles; Green, Sol; Green, Frederick; Hausman, Howard L.] (14-0-563 to 14-0-569), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Nugent, Elliott; Henried, Paul; Massey, Raymond; Laughton, Charles; Wilde, Cornel; Mead, Dr. Margaret] (14-0-570 to 14-0-575), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Hurwitz, Leo; Schwartz, Arthur; Huston, Walter; Horne, Lena; Lindsay, Howard; Tone, Franchot] (14-0-576 to 14-0-581), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Blanvalet, Lothar; Birnbaum, Morton; Bonnell, Rev. Dr. John Sutherland; Bromsen, William E.] (14-0-582 to 14-0-587), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Churchill, Winston; Bevah, Aneurin; Bon, M.J.; Barnes, Fred P.; Balabanoff, Dr. Angelica] (14-0-588 to 14-0-606), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lerner, Max; Ordower, Sidney; Straus, Michael W.; Anderson, Franklin J.; Kingdon, Dr. Frank; Seymour, Charles] (14-0-607 to 14-0-617), 1940-1941, 1947-1949 (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lazorek, Elizabeth; Unger, Abraham; Jones, Thomas Russell; Rosenblum, Irwin; Pell, Herbert] (14-0-618 to 14-0-623), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Harrington, Rev. Donald; Kelley, Rev. William J.; Colby, Bainbridge; Wahrhaftig, Samuel L.; Stalcup, Mr. and Mrs. Caroll] (14-0-624 to 14-0-635), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [McLean, Dean C.; Carroll, Charles O.; Shorett, Lloyd; Anderson, Dr. Dewey; Blackett, Prof. Patrick M.S.] (14-0-636 to 14-0-656), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 50)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Cole, Rev. Franklin P.; Chapin, Howard M.; Canham, Erwin D.; Coleman, Earl; Cieplak, Marian Bogdan] (14-0-657 to 14-0-667), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 51)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [McMichael, Rev. Jack R.; Coryell, Pierce Allen; Christensen, Julia; Case, Walter (a.k.a. Chester Casey), Cushman, Dr. Robert E.] (14-0-668 to 14-0-676), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 52)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [McKay, Claude; Maier, Rev. Dr. Walter A.; Matchavariani, Venjamin N.; McCracken, Rev. Dr. Robert J.; Martens, Ludwig Christian Adolf Karl] (14-0-677 to 14-0-683), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Myers, Fred; Meany, George; Maslow, Will; Margold, Stella K.; Masaryk, Jan; Mather, Prof. Kirtley F.; Meyer, Hershel] (14-0-684 to 14-0-699), 1947-1949 (Box 13, Folder 54)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Menagh, Donald F.; Monroe, Henry; Meisler, George; Melby, Ernest O.; Marcotti, Jack C.; Maguire, Edward C.; Matthews, Francis P.] (14-0-700 to 14-0-709), 1947-1949 (Box 13, Folder 55)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [McCarthy, Glenn; Murra, John V.; Moon, Henry Lee; Mann, Klaus; Morse, Wayne; Morrison, De Lesseps S.] (14-0-710 to 14-0-718), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Marsalka, Prof. John M.; McCollum, Vashti; Potter, Dr. Charles Francis; Graham, Dr. Frank Porter; Matthews, Dr. Joseph B.] (14-0-719 to 14-0-725), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 57)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Fairchild, Henry Pratt; Swing, Raymond; Vaudo, Salvatore; Douglas, Helen Gahagan; Mitchell, John] (14-0-726 to 14-0-732), 1942, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Sorrell, Herbert K.; Bioff, Willie; Seeger, Peter; Camargo, Florence; Shireer, William L.; Somers, Andrew L.] (14-0-733 to 14-0-739), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Seldes, George; Roosevelt, Eleanor; Shirer, William L.; Schutzer, Arthur; Struik, Dr. Dirk J.; Snow, Russell W., Jr.; Sugrue, Tom] (14-0-740 to 14-0-745), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 60)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Schneiderman, Rose; Smith, General Walter Bedell; Soss, Wilma; Stuart, Dr. John Leighton; Schieffelin, William Jay; Sinclair, Upton] (14-0-746 to 14-0-752), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 61)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Burdett, Mrs. Harold S.; Sloan, Allan E.; Sullivan, Lawrence; Steinhardt, Laurence A.; Struik, Dirk J.; Sasieff, Boris] (14-0-753 to 14-0-763), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 62)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Shenkar, George; Sasuly, Elizabeth; Stuart, John Leighton; Marshall, George C.; Sheehy, Rev. Maurice S.; Schmidt, Godfrey P.] (14-0-764 to 14-0-779), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 63)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Steed, Tom; Sullivan, Mark; Spitz, David; Stachtopoulos, Gregory; Sario, John; Thompson, Rev. Dr. John B.] (14-0-780 to 14-0-786), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 64)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Schneider, Aaron D.; Schutzer, Arthur; Studer, Norman; Sotirov, Dr. George D.; Kaye, Arthur; Shelvey, Matt] (14-0-787 to 14-0-805), 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 65)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Devoto, Bernard; Felix, David H.H.; Goddard, Howard; Raphael, Martin; Mellow, Greta; Drake, Alfred; Curiano, John and Rose Busin] (14-0-806 to 14-0-814), 1940, 1949 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Bergstrom, R.W.; McDonald, George; De Maio, Ernest and Anthony; Matles, James J.; Pomerantz, Abraham; Wild, Payson Sibley Jr.] (14-0-815 to 14-0-821), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Seaver, Edwin; Gruenberg, Sidonie Matsner; Fitzgerald, Albert J.; Emspak, Julius; Hathaway, Clarence A.; Mauseth, William] (14-0-822 to 14-0-827), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Nathan, Robert; Hastie, William H.; Piscator, Erwin; Kaplan, Morris J.; Ruskin, Coby; Gorney, Jay; Jacobs, Lewis; Gorney, Sandra] (14-0-828 to 14-0-835), 1949 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Littledale, Clara Savage; Lancaster, Burt; Friedman, Morton; Royle, Selena; Obermeier, Michael J.; Frooks, Dorothy; Hallinan, Vincent] (14-0-836 to 14-0-843), 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 70)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Latimer, Ira; Logan, Ella; Bryan, Julien; Swing, Raymond (Gram); Kaye, Danny; Limbert, Paul M.; Cooper, Gary] (14-0-844 to 14-0-850), 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Shaw, Irwin; Lardner, John; Mundy, Meg; Daniels, Marc; Vertanes, Rev. Charles A.; Meredith, Burgess] (14-0-851 to 14-0-856), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Morrison, Philip; Revyuk, Emil; Jacobi, Frederick; Fosdick, Dr. Harry Emerson; Halper, Albert; Levy, Newman; Minus, Mariah] (14-0-857 to 14-0-863), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 73)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Duff, Howard; Lyon, Peter; Parodneck, Meyer; Cobb, Lee J.; Gold, William J.; Bryan, Julien; Fielding, Michael; Untermeyer, Louis] (14-0-864 to 14-0-872), 1948-1950 (Box 13, Folder 74)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Stuart, Maryland; Hughes, Rupert; Wicker, Ireene; Kimball, Penn; Tisa, John; Everett, Ethel; Conway, Curt; Sullivan, Elliott] (14-0-873 to 14-0-879), 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 75)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Callahan, Joseph (Pat); Hansen, Charles; Hammer, Victor J.; Edmonds, Walter D.; Zugsmith, Leane; Lieber, Maxim; Billington, Ray A.] (14-0-880 to 14-0-886), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 76)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Warnick, Jack; Davey, Charles; Dardeck, Samuel; Panchelly, Anthony; Brown, Donald N.; Bremmer, Leroy; Chambers, Patrick (Pat) E.] (14-0-887 to 14-0-893), 1941 (Box 13, Folder 77)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Posner, Harry; Rosenweig, Sam; Balint, David; Balint, Alex; Ambrose, Vance Earl; Crouch, Paul M.; Fields, Benjamin; Glynn, Melville] (14-0-894 to 14-0-902), 1941 (Box 13, Folder 78)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Thompson, Robert; Winter, Carl; Suttka, Jesse F.; Woodward, Edward; Whalen, Patrick; Hoffman, Jack; Potash, Irving] (14-0-903 to 14-0-909), 1941, undated (Box 13, Folder 79)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Alberts, Seymour Bernard; Acheson, Dean; Arshan, Benjamin; Davis, Benjamin J., Jr.; Green, Gil; Hall, Gus; Potash, Irving] (14-0-910 to 14-0-920), 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 80)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Alth, Aurel; Alexeev, Kirill; Hiskey, Clarence F.; Addes, George; Altman, Jack; Alfred, Helen L.; Adams, Samuel Hopkins; Anderson, Marian] (14-0-921 to 14-0-930), 1947-1950 (Box 13, Folder 81)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Barry, Walter; Brown, John Mason; Bruce, Virginia; Bettis, Valerie; Bogart, Humphrey; Bankhead, Tallulah; Budenz, Louis Francis] (14-0-931 to 14-0-938), 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 82)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Basie, William "Count"; Bergson, Abram; Binger, Dr. Carl; Bailey, Dorothy; Bryson, Hugh; Byrnes, Robert Charles; Baron, Sam] (14-0-939 to 14-0-945), 1948-1950 (Box 13, Folder 83)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Clark, Pauline M.; Cotten, Joseph; Cagney, James; Chodorov, Edward; Banning, Margaret Culkin; Baker, Mary Mullins] (14-0-946 to 14-0-951), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 84)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Dryden, Robert; Dekker, Albert; Denny, George V., Jr.; Davidson, Maurice P.; Culbertson, Ely; Clement, Mary Romig; Conway, Joseph] (14-0-952 to 14-0-961], 1950 (Box 13, Folder 85)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Haldane, J.B.S.; Ellington, Duke; Epstein, Israel; Evans, Bergen; Eric, Elspeth; Ellis, William D.; Douglas, Melvyn; Davis, Bette; Davis, Garry] (14-0-962 to 14-0-971), 1948, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 86)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Huston, Walter; Hindus, Maurice; Hill, Stephen; Hewitt, Alan; Herrman, Bernard; Heller, Robert P.; Hazard, John N.; Hardwicke, Sir Cedric] (14-0-972 to 14-0-980), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 87)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Gaer, Joseph; Gabel, Martin; Fontaine, Joan; Fisher, Dr. Harold; Finn, William J.; Ferguson, Rev. D. Leroy; Felsen, Henry Gregor] (14-0-981 to 14-0-987), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 88)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Orfink, Michael; Ostendorf, Ludwig Dietrich; Guthrie, Anne; Greenberg, Jacob; Gorodnitzki, Sacha; Gilmore, H. Farrell; Garrett, Mary V.] (14-0-988 to 14-0-995), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 89)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Monath, Hortense; Mott, Prof. Frank Luther; Mangold, Helen; Meyers, Ben; Miles, Dr. Virginia; Mencher, Max] (14-0-996 to 14-0-1001), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 90)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Mann, Paul; McCormick, Myron; Miller, Mitchell; MacLeish, Archibald; Murphy, Rev. Amos C. Barstow; Malina, Luba] (14-0-1002 to 14-0-1007), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 91)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lewis, John (Lenio); LaGallienne, Eva; Leyda, Jay; Lee, Canada; Lindeman, Eduard; Marion, Ira; Mayer, C. Henry; Mosely, Philip E.] (14-0-1008 to 14-0-1015), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 92)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Lewis, Harry; Irving, Charles; Harris, Judge Norval K.; Kearney, William Francis; Lyon, Peter; Laird, Donald A. and Eleanor C.] (14-0-1016 to 14-0-1022), 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 93)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Heisman, Sadie K.; Heisman, Robert M.; Appel, Abraham and Frances; Carus, Herbert; Johnson, Ray; Johnson, Dallas; Levine, Murray S.] (14-0-1023 to 14-0-1028), 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 94)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Rodriguez, Anthony; Rosen, George; Raskin, Jack; Royle, Selena; Robbins, Jerome; Raymond, Ellsworth Lester] (14-0-1029 to 14-0-1034), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 95)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Ritchie, Catheryn; Powell, Adam Clayton, Jr.; Robinson, Geroid Tanquary; Rose, Anna Perrott; Rainer, Luise; Ryan, John F.] (14-0-1035 to 14-0-1040), 1947-1950 (Box 13, Folder 96)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Woods, J.B. Collins; Wexley, John (a.k.a. Jacob Wechsler); Pauling, Linus; Toorchen, Hal and Jan; Velson, Irving; Price, Vincent; Pious, Minerva] (14-0-1041 to 14-0-1047), 1948-1950 (Box 13, Folder 97)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Shaw, Robert; Searle, Dr. Robert W.; Scott, Hazel; Rhode, Ruth Bryan Owen; Shub, Louis; Swing, Raymond (Gram); Sentner, William] (14-0-1048 to 14-0-1054), 1948-1950 (Box 13, Folder 98)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Smith, Edwin Seymour; Ross, Lillian; Smith, Hilda Worthington; Vernadsky, George; Tone, Franchot; Van Orden, Katherine Armitage] (14-0-1055 to 14-0-1060), 1948-1950 (Box 13, Folder 99)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Vaughn, Hilda; Wolfe, Dr. Hugh C.; Powell, John H.; Paley, Jack; Payne, Paul Calvin; Rosinger, Lawrence K.; Sayers, Michael] (14-0-1061 to 14-0-1067), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 100)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Schieffelin, Dr. William J.; Witt, Herbert; Winters, Shelley; Wertheimer, Joan; Wayne, David; Voss, Dr. Carl Hermann; Van Doren, Dorothy] (14-0-1068 to 14-0-1074), 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 101)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Williams, Herb; Ward, Theodore; Royster, Wallace E.; Pedi, Tom; Sloane, Everett; Shepherd, Ann; Sandburg, Carl; Smith, David] (14-0-1075 to 14-0-1082), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Tone, Franchot; Rosenberg, Milton; Terlin, Rose; Sloane, William; Sullivan, Richard; Sylvester, John; Sherman, Hiram; Ward, Albert; Warne, William E.] (14-0-1083 to 14-0-1092), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Friedman, Joseph; Goodman, Jack; Crichton, Kyle; Foner, Philip S.; Cody, Martin; Cobb, Lee J.; Mayer, Edwin Justus; Robinson, Earl] (14-0-1093 to 14-0-1101), 1947, 1949-1950 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Nichol, Herbert J.; Van Gelder, Philip H.; Nathan, Robert; McAvoy, Clifford T.; Nowack, Stanley; Hackett, Albert; Garramone, Mike] (14-0-1102 to 14-0-1107), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Allen, Frances Fowler; Adler, F. Charles; Segal, Martin E.; Lederer, Howard W. and Anne Hilda; Sweets, William; Niebuhr, Reinhold] (14-0-1108 to 14-0-1114), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Smith, Frank Leon; Scott, Margaret; Russell, Prof. Phillips; Rose, Dorothy E.; Neuwirth, Morris; Morrissey, Bill; Miller, John; Carter, Marjorie] (14-0-1115 to 14-0-1122), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Jaffe, Henry; Jackson, Eugene; Harris, James E.; Greenfield, Samuel; Gilman, William; Diamond, Max; Case, Meyer; Boudin, Leonard] (14-0-1123 to 14-0-1133), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Thomas, Dorothy; Stern, Isaac; Smith, Elsie Gould; Plamondon, Edythe; Needleman, Morriss; Koenig, Helmut; Kell, Reginald] (14-0-1134 to 14-0-1143), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Williamson, Mel; Taylor, Dr. Harold; Taylor, Davidson; Smith, Howard K.; Ward, Elizabeth B.; Wallach, Samuel; Waldbaum, Saul C.] (14-0-1144 to 14-0-1151), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 110)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Neibuhr, Reinhold; Nathan, Robert; Muste, Rev. A. J.; Sloan, Lavinia Janes; Sherrill, Bishop Henry Knox; Schulberg, Budd W.; Wright, Archie] (14-0-1152 to 14-0-1158), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 111)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Mather, Kirtley F.; Hurok, Sol; Hausman, Howard L.; Scherer, Marcel; Schain, Josephine; Rubin, Samuel; Rubin, Milton; O'Keefe, Winston] (14-0-1159 to 14-0-1167), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 112)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Hoffman, Mrs. K.L.; Johson, Isabel; Hymes, James L., Jr.; Hughes, Langston; MacLeish, Archibald; Mack, Richard; Miller, Merle] (14-0-1168 to 14-0-1175), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 113)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Cantor, Eddie; Garland, Charles Stedman; Dodson, Dan W.; Devine, Edward; Corsi, Edward; Corey, Paul; Cone, Fairfax Mastick] (14-0-1176 to 14-0-1182), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 114)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Hammond, John Hayes; Dolivet, Louis; Robinson, Edward G.; O'Keefe, Winston; Hocking, William Ernest; Einstein, Albert; Cobb, Lee J.; Baldwin, C.B.] (14-0-1183 to 14-0-1192), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 115)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Gold, Horace Leonard; Corcos, Lucille; Barnes, Joseph; Stewart, Mrs. Alexander; Reynolds,. Quentin; Reuther, Walter Philip; Palmer, Charles B.] (14-0-1193 to 14-0-1200), 1950 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Rosenberg, Anna M.; Levine, Israel E.; Lederer, Howard W.; Krauss, Janet Phyliss; Eby, Kermit; Stone, Victoria; Savo, Jimmy] (14-0-1201 to 14-0-1210), 1950 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Pauling, Dr. Linus; St. John, Robert; Shirer, William L.; Rogers, Fred; McMahon, Lucile Nelson; Gross, Marion; Gleason, Leverett S.] (14-0-1211 to 14-0-1217), 1950 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Karwatt, Sonia; Carse, Robert and Janet Wood; Schriftgiesser, Karl; Ruthenberg, Charles; Finney, Burnham; Conte, Richard; Burke, Robert] (14-0-1218 to 14-0-1224), 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Close, Upton; Calhern, Louis; Buck, Pearl S.; Bogart, Humphrey; Bacall, Lauren; Adams, Franklin P.] (14-0-1225 to 14-0-1230), 1950-1951 (Box 14, Folder 5)